Guide to the The Inquiry Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Oversize Maps (Miscellaneous Printed Materials), 1856, 1868-1919
  - Russia
    - Brest-Litovsk line from "Vorwaerts", 495 (Folder 36O)
    - Latvia & Lithuania, 782 (Folder 36O)
      Marked on portion of A.G.S. base.
    - Seat of Ukraine Republic (on tracing linen), 557 (Folder 36O)
    - Ukraine & Transcaucasia, 661 (Folder 36O)
      Photostat of A.G.S. base with linguistic frontier added.
    - (Caucasus, outline, showing line outside of which Germany pledged herself to keep forces of any 3 powers), 560 (Folder 36O)
      On linen.
    - Boundary of Ukraine, 534 (Folder 36O)
      On tracing paper, 2 prints.
    - Military operations in Russia, 673 (Folder 36O)
      On tracing linen, & 2 photostats.
    - Military operations in Siberia (photostat), 674 (Folder 36O)
    - Military situation in Russia from information received up to Jan 29, 1919, Eastern Europe and Asia. (Folder 36O)
      Base by Printing Plant, 29th Engrs., U.S. Army, 1919.
    - Eastern Europe ports and waterways (photostat), 763 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia. Workmen employed in textile industires of European Russia, 547, 1913 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia. Workmen employed in manufacturing of iron, steel, etc. (photostat), 548, 1913 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia. Workmen employed in manufactiring. of lumber, etc., 549, 1913 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia. Workmen employed in munfacturing industries as % of local population, 545 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia. Workmen employed in sugar refining…, 550 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia. Workmen employed in manufacturing industries, 544, 1913 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia Local workers employed in manufacturing industries, as % of total Russian workers, 546, 1913 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia Local workers employed in textile industries, 547, 1913 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia local crop acreage as % of Russian total, 552 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia % of land area used for crops, 551 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia Excess or deficiency in wheat production as compared with needs, 553 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia (untitled photostat, city grades), 554 (Folder 36O)
    - Bessarabia. 1:3,500,000, 538 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia. 1:4,500,000 (2 sheets) Geo. Philip & Son, 1918-1919 (Folder 36O)
  - Turkey
    - A.G.S. base map 1:6,000,000, 730 (Folder 36A)
      Colored to show mandates and railways.
    - A.G.S. base map 1:6,000,000 Zones of influence or territorial acquisitions (also photostat reduction), 611 (Folder 36A)
    - A.G.S. base map 1:6,000,000 Sykes-Picot map to ill agreements of 1916 (and photostat reduction, colored), 729 (Folder 36A)
    - A.G.S. base map 1:6,000,000 (Folder 36A)
      Railways added.
    - A.G.S. base map 1:6,000,000 (Folder 36A)
      Showing British conquests and Greek claims.
    - Turkey -- 2 maps, 56 & 627 (Folder 36A)
    - A.G.S. base map 1:6,000,000, Anatolia and Armenie, 82 (Folder 36A)
    - Turkey.
      - Population by a numbers (photostat), 614 (Folder 36A)
      - Population by percentages (photostat), 615 (Folder 36A)
    - Turkey. Rainfall, 561 (Folder 36A)
      Photostat reduction of A.G.S. base.
    - Asia Minor. Linguistic boundary. 666 (Folder 36A)
      Base is reduction of 627.
    - Map showing frontier rectification between Turkey and Bulgaria, according to Treaty of 1915 (2 copies), 533 (Folder 36A)
    - Proposed boundaries of Armenia, 787 (Folder 36A)
    - Lines claimed by M. Venezelos, and Franco-British proposal, 728 (Folder 36A)
      Base is photostat reduction of 627; also plotted on Istanbul sheet, War Office map of Europe 1/M.
    - Territory in Asia Minor to be given to Greece, 725 (Folder 36A)
      On tracing paper and photostat.
    - Constantinople area and Greek Asia (linguistic boundary), 650 (Folder 36A)
    - Region around Constantinople (2 copies), 771 (Folder 36A)
    - A proposed Armeno-Caucasian Confederation, 700 (Folder 36A)
    - Map of E. Turkey in Asia… Ethnographic G.S.G.S. 2901 1910-1917 (Folder 36A)
    - Provinces of Asia Minor (Folder 36A)
      Penciled sketch, includes Balkans.
    - Turkey & Greece. Boundaries as sketched by M. Venizelos, 607, 1918 December 18 (Folder 36A)
      On A.G.S. base I/3M; and photostat reduction.
  - Yugoslavia
    - Population density, 764 (Folder 36N)
      Hand colored, and photostat reduction.
    - Jugo Slav boundaries (on tracing paper), 714 (Folder 36N)
    - Railways of Jugoslav countries -- D.J. Derocco, Paris, 1919 (Folder 36N)
    - Carte des regions Yougo-slavs. Editions Bossard (Folder 36N)
    - Serb Frontier in the Banat & Backa (linguistic boundary), 669 (Folder 36N)
    - Proposed division of Serbia between Austria and Bulgaria (2 copies), 499 and two drawings on linen, 498 (Folder 36N)
  - Africa
    - A.G.S. base 1:26,500,000, 2 (Folder 36B)
    - A.G.S. base 1:10,000,000 Northwest Africa, 2a-1 (Folder 36B)
    - A.G.S. base 1:10,000,000 Northeast Africa, 2a-2 (Folder 36B)
    - A.G.S. base 1:10,000,000 South Africa, 2a-3 (Folder 36B)
    - A.G.S. base 1:10,000,000 Central Africa, 2a-4 (Folder 36B)
    - A.G.S. base 1:10,000,000 1:18,000,000 Central Africa, 5a (Folder 36B)
    - A.G.S. base 1:10,000,000 1:18,000,000 Central Africa (photostat), 518 (Folder 36B)
    - A.G.S base (showing international agreements), 641 (Folder 36B)
    - Carte du Monde au 1,000,000. Diagramme de reparttiton des Feuilles d'Afrique. 1:20,000,000, 143 (Folder 36B)
    - Cessions of French Territory in Africa, (Cameroons), 643, 1911 November 4 (Folder 36B)
    - (Outline map of Africa, showing railways & German colonies), 693 (Folder 36B)
    - Italian claims in North Africa, 676 (Folder 36B)
    - Kameroons. Ethnographic (drawing and photostat reduction), 703 (Folder 36B)
    - Togoland. Ethnographic (drawing and photostat reduction), 698 (Folder 36B)
    - German East Africa Ethnographic (drawing and photostat reduction), 697 (Folder 36B)
    - German East Africa Population (drawing & photostat reduction), 696 (Folder 36B)
  - Asia
    - A.G.S. base 1/20,000,000, 10a (Folder 36C)
    - A.G.S 1/12,000,000 Danube to India, 22a (Folder 36C)
    - A.G.S 1/13,000,000 Western Asia, 18a (Folder 36C)
    - (part of Siberia 1/5,000,000), 628 (Folder 36C)
      Covering Central Asia.
    - Arabia (outline) (Folder 36C)
    - (spheres of influence; drawing & photostat), 690 (Folder 36C)
    - (British Territory), 670 (Folder 36C)
    - Rainfall, 521 (Folder 36C)
    - (outline, reduced photostat), 629 (Folder 36C)
    - Syria. A.G.S. base. 1:1,000,000, 41a (Folder 36C)
    - Palestine A.G.S base 1:1,000,000, 42a (Folder 36C)
    - (Palestine and Syria, combined War Office maps, marked to show boundaries claimed), 772 (Folder 36C)
    - China. Treaty Ports, 520 (Folder 36C)
    - China. 760 (Folder 36C)
      MS drawing, showing railways, canals, etc., 8 prints.
    - (Manchuria, Korea, etc. base. colored photostat), 689 (Folder 36C)
    - Russian and Japanese influence along the Chinese Eastern Ry., 705 (Folder 36C)
    - (Lands around the Yellow Sea; base, with railways), 694 & 694a (Folder 36C)
    - (Lands around the Yellow Sea; base, photostat, 9 prints), 724 (Folder 36C)
    - Etat Chinoise (photostat), 691 (Folder 36C)
    - Shantung, 701 (Folder 36C)
    - Mongolia, 677 (Folder 36C)
    - Mongolia linguistic, 706 (Folder 36C)
    - China map of Tibet or Bod. (MS drawing), 559 (Folder 36C)
  - General Miscellaneous (Folder 36M)